var questions = {
    1: {
        question: "What is the name of the ball with a start that appears in many Pixar films?",
        answer: "The Luxo Ball",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Bouncers",
            "Andy's Ball",
            "The BNL Ball"
        ]
    },
    2: {
        question: "What year was Pixar started?",
        answer: "1986",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "1995",
            "1988",
            "2001"
        ]
    },
    3: {
        question: "Who is the sea turtle who helps out Marlin and Dory in \"Finding Nemo\"?",
        answer: "Crush",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Primo",
            "Bro",
            "Crunch"
        ]
    },
    4: {
        question: "What magical creatures lead Merida to a witch in \"Brave\"?",
        answer: "Will O' The Wisps",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Goblins",
            "Fairies",
            "Ghosts"
        ]
    },
    5: {
        question: "What fraternity does Mike Wazowski join in \"Monsters University\"?",
        answer: "OOZMA KAPPA",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "SIGMA FEAR OMEGA",
            "ROAR OMEGA ROAR",
            "ALPHA SCAREMS"
        ]
    },
    6: {
        question: "Before he became Syndrome, he wore rocket boots and called himself what?",
        answer: "Incrediboy",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "The Aviator",
            "Rocket Boy",
            "Incredikid"
        ]
    },
    7: {
        question: "Who said...\"That wasn't flying! That was falling with style!\" (Toy Story)?",
        answer: "Woody",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Rex",
            "Buzz Lightyear",
            "Jesse"
        ]
    },
    8: {
        question: "Who is the boy who terrifies the toys in \"Toy Story\"?",
        answer: "Sid",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Andy",
            "Buster",
            "Al"
        ]
    },
    8: {
        question: "Who voiced Lighting McQueen in \"Cars\"?",
        answer: "Owen Wilson",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Adrien Brody",
            "Bradley Cooper",
            "Ben Stiller"
        ]
    },
    9: {
        question: "In \"The Good Dinosaur\", how do Arlo and Spot start communicating?",
        answer: "By drawing pictures",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "A gorilla-like body language",
            "Sign language",
            "Just regular talking"
        ]
    },
    10: {
        question: "On what planet was Wall-E stranded at the beginning of \"Wall-E\"?",
        answer: "Earth",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Mars",
            "Wall-E World",
            "It wasn't named"
        ]
    },
    11: {
        question: "In \"Finding Dory\", Dory is lucky to find a friend in an octopus with how many tentacles?",
        answer: "7",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "6",
            "8",
            "5"
        ]
    },
    12: {
        question: "The letter-number combination \"A113\" can be found semi-hidden in every Pixar feature film. What does it refer to?",
        answer: "A Classroom",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Steve Jobs's First Car",
            "The First Pixar Short Film",
            "Pixar's name when it was still a top-secret project"
        ]
    },
    13: {
        question: "Who said...\"I do not like the cone of shame.\" (Up)?",
        answer: "Dug",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Charles Muntz",
            "Carl",
            "Russell"
        ]
    },
    14: {
        question: "Who said...\"I never look back, darling. It distracts from the now.\" (The Incredibles)?",
        answer: "Edna Mode",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Mr. Incredible",
            "Frozone",
            "Elastigirl"
        ]
    },
    15: {
        question: "What is the name of the main food critic in \"Ratatouille\"?",
        answer: "Anton Ego",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Nolan Argo",
            "Tony Angelo",
            "Aron Ergo"
        ]
    },
    16: {
        question: "On what structure does each member of the family \"make their mark\" in \"The Good Dinosaur\"?",
        answer: "The Corn Silo",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "The House",
            "The Barn",
            "The Chicken Pen"
        ]
    },
    17: {
        question: "What is Wall-E's primary function?",
        answer: "Garbage Compactor",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Loading and Unloading",
            "Maintenance Robot",
            "To alert earth's survivors to the reemergence of plant life"
        ]
    },
    18: {
        question: "Which of these voice actors has appeared in every Pixar film so far?",
        answer: "John Ratzenberger",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Tom Hanks",
            "Joan Cusack",
            "John Goodman"
        ]
    },
    19: {
        question: "What classic musical does Wall-E enjoy watching and dancing along to?",
        answer: "Hello, Dolly!",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "West Side Story",
            "The Sound of Music",
            "My Fair Lady"
        ]
    },
    20: {
        question: "What does Boo call Sulley in \"Monsters, Inc.\"?",
        answer: "Kitty",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Fuzzy",
            "Doggy",
            "Bear"
        ]
    },
    21: {
        question: "In \"Toy Story 3\", the toys find themselves stuck in this daycare facility?",
        answer: "Sunnyside",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Happy Huggers",
            "Lala Land",
            "Learning Ladder"
        ]
    },
    22: {
        question: "What is the city where \"Monsters, Inc.\" takes place?",
        answer: "Monstropolis",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Terror Town",
            "Boo York",
            "Monster City"
        ]
    },
    23: {
        question: "Why does the food critic begin to cry when he tastes the ratatouille in \"Ratatouille\"?",
        answer: "Beacuse it reminds him of his mother",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Because it's terrible",
            "Beacuse it reminds him of his late best friend",
            "Beacuse it makes him feel like a fraud"
        ]
    },
    24: {
        question: "Finish this quote from Ellie to Carl in \"Up\": \"Thanks for the adventure, now...\"",
        answer: "Go have a new one.",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Do something fun!",
            "Get to South America!",
            "Do something crazy!"
        ]
    },
    25: {
        question: "Lighting McQueen is sentenced to community service doing what in \"Cars\"?",
        answer: "Repaving the road he damaged",
        wrongAnswers: [
            "Acting as a cross guard",
            "Cleaning the highway",
            "Volunteering at a local school"
        ]
    },
}